Trista McCleary

<u>CodeAndCoffeeLife.com</u> <u>github.com/mccleary</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/tristamccleary</u> 404-376-2653 Atlanta,Ga trista_mccleary@yahoo.com

Summary

Strongly detail-oriented person with a love for organization and eager to apply those skills to web development. Excited to continue to grow my web development skills and am looking for employers who make my continued learning a priority. Ideally, I'd like to work on a team of developers who enjoy their craft, are building interesting software, and who are open to mentoring and developing new talent. I am an eternal student and it's exciting to me that there is so much out there to learn, and I look forward to continuing to add to my skill set for many years to come.

Projects

FITLIFE

FitLife is a fitness eCommerce site designed to help those looking to learn how to eat properly, get healthy and lose weight. Meal plans are offered for both men and women. Look for workout plans coming soon! This project was made with the MEAN stack(JavaScript, jQuery, Node, Express, Angular, MongoDB)

Github: github.com/mccleary/fitlife

Demo: http://fitlifeforlife.us:5000/#/

GETCOHORT

GetCohort is a Coding Bootcamp app built to showcase each student's projects and contact info as well as links to their email, portfolio, github and linkedIn sites. This was a week long project built with a scrum team of four developers using agile development methodologies. Technologies used: HTML/CSS, Python, Flask, PostgreSQL. *My class group project tied for second place!

Github: https://github.com/DigitalCrafts-September-2016-Cohort/GetCohort

Demo: <u>http://54.148.11.254/</u> (for testing - user: juan.cortes@gmail.com | pass: 1)

PIXEL ART MAKER

Pixel Art Maker is a single page web app that lets users draw a pixel image on a customizable panel. Users can create their own grid size, choose their own color(s), fill the entire grid with a single color, and drag colors to create their own pixel art. Technologies used: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Github: https://github.com/mccleary/Pixel-Art-Maker

Demo: https://mccleary.github.io/Pixel-Art-Maker/

Education

DigitalCrafts, Ga - Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

Clayton State University, Ga - AAS, Computer Networking

Clayton State University, Ga - Certificate, Computer Network Technician

Clayton State University, Ga - BBA, Business Management

Skills

- Web Development
- Software Training
- Purchasing Management
- Supply Chain Management Event Planning Project Management

- Vendor Management
- VMI/Consignment Inventory

- MRP/Inventory Control
- Production/Production Planning
- Sourcing
- Lean Manufacturing Concepts
- Customer Relations
 Staff Training/Team Building
- Multi-Level/Multi-location
- Continuous Improvement

Experience

INSIDE SALES REP/PROCESSING SPECIALIST/INFRA-CHAMPION, INFRA-METALS - 2011-2015

- Handled three of the largest processing accounts in the company, retained highest gross margin profit.
- Manage job quotations and tracking process while focusing on driving company's margin product line. Responsible for account development and new business prospecting in a highly competitive market.
- Perform general sales functions -quotes, create job bids using T27 System based on duration of project length, data entry of sales, customer, quotes and invoices, apply industry knowledge, policies and procedures for questions and concerns posed while ensuring safety, scheduling of trucks with other departments to ensure commitment to the customer/client, Carbon Steel, Stainless, Aluminum.
- Software Trainer for co-workers on new Sales Software system Eniteo after company buyout

SOUTHEAST SENIOR BUYER, DIETRICH METAL FRAMING - 1998-2010

- Provided direction and leadership for more than 20 company buyers of manufacturing consumables; contained and reduced costs through successful price negotiations and vendor management, aided in efficient operation of purchasing policies and procedures, and ensured conformance to company purchasing objectives and policies.
- Consistently maintained supply chain flow, thus minimizing downtime and maximizing productivity. Software Trainer, Managed and trained buyers in Oracle, I-Procurement, Contempus, SOX compliance. Managed buyers for ten facilities in the Southeast and Midwest and purchased supplies for four facilities; provided back up purchasing for 25 additional locations.
- Achieved cost reduction of 10.5% (\$85K in six months) by identifying inventory efforts and managing reduction of manufacturing expenses through vendor consolidation, renegotiation of service contracts, freight reductions, and changing items being purchased.

Professional Organizations

PyLadiesATL - Member (Fall 2016 - present)

Women Who Code Atlanta - Member (Fall 2016 - present)